Crusade for Opportunity Records
Crusade for Opportunity Records
- Research files
  - Code sheets
    - Inner city recreation, 1965; 2 folders (Box 242)
    - Instructions for stat clerks (coding), 1966 (Box 242)
    - Interview code sheet - Ise, 1966 (Box 242)
    - Inventory of punched cards, undated (Box 242)
    - James-Geddes pre-school control, undated (Box 242)
    - Job Corp, 1966 (Box 242)
    - Legal, deck I and II, undated; 2 folders (Box 242)
    - Lists - East, West, North, Upper East Side camperships (intake), 1965 (Box 242)
    - Madison school, codebook, 1965 (Box 242)
    - Memos regarding education section, 1965 (Box 242)
    - Near North Side community service, 1967; 2 folders (Box 242)
    - Neighborhood surveys, cards I-II, 1967; 6 folders (Box 242)
    - Neighborhood surveys, cards I-II, 1967; 2 folders (Box 243)
    - Neighborhood survey code, 1965 (Box 243)
    - North Side community services, 1967; 3 folders (Box 243)
    - North Side individual contact, Sep 1967 (Box 243)
    - Numbers to be assigned, 1967 (Box 243)
    - Numeric, all programs, 1966 (Oversize 1)
    - Old deck I and II code books, 1965 (Box 243)
    - On-the-Job placements, deck X, 1964-1965 (Box 243)
    - Original codebooks, education, 1964-1965 (Box 243)
    - Personnel inventory code, 1966 (Box 243)
    - Personnel inventory deck I, 1966 (Box 243)
    - Personnel inventory, termination code, 1966; 2 folders (Box 243)
    - Pioneer base
      - Pioneer base, 1966; 4 folders (Box 243)
      - Community service, 1966-1967; 9 folders (Box 243)
      - Help Center, community service, 1966; 2 folders (Box 243)
      - Study Center, 1966-1967; 4 folders (Box 243)
    - Pioneer Center, participant group, May 1967 (Box 243)
    - Pioneer Center study center, Mar 1967 (Box 243)
    - Pioneer homes, 1966 (Box 243)
    - Pioneer home community service, 1966 (Box 243)
    - Pioneer homes pre-school control, undated (Box 243)
    - Preschool, Deck I card N, 1966 (Box 243)
    - Preschool, Delaware Baptist, 1966; 2 folders (Box 243)
    - Preschool, Dunbar, 1966; 2 folders (Box 243)
    - Preschool Washington Irving, 1966; 2 folders (Box 243)
    - Problem code, help center and detached workers, 1964-1965 (Box 243)
    - Project Head Start, codebook I, 1965 (Box 244)
    - Punching estimates, 1966 (Box 244)
    - Qualitative reading responses, 1964-1965 (Box 244)
    - Reading termination and evaluation, 1965; 2 folders (Box 244)
    - Recreation, deck II, undated (Box 244)
    - Recreation inner city intake, 1965 (Box 244)
    - Recreation intake, volunteers, not coded, 1965 (Box 244)
    - Reentry, 1965; 3 folders (Box 244)
    - Rehab deck I card I, 1966 (Box 244)
    - Rehab code book, part I, undated (Box 244)
    - Rehab termination and evaluation, 1966 (Box 244)
    - Rehabilitation, deck I card N, 1966 (Box 244)
    - Rehabilitation classes, 1964-1965 (Box 244)
    - Research feedbacks, 1965-1966 (Box 244)
    - Revised edition, deck one card one, Feb 1966 (Box 244)
    - Roosevelt study center, 1965-1966; 10 folders (Box 244)
    - Self-reported demographic characteristics, deck I card O, employment termination codebook, 1966 (Box 244)
    - Seymour
      - Group guidance opinion poll, 1966 (Box 245)
      - Guidance, 1966 (Box 245)
      - Guidance intake form, 1965 (Box 245)
      - Individual guidance, 1966; 3 folders (Box 245)
      - School-opinion poll code sheets, group guidance, 1965 (Box 245)
      - Study center research, Sep 1966 (Box 245)
    - Shonnard recreation, intake forms, 1965 (Box 245)
    - Shonnard Street lot, deck II, undated (Box 245)
    - Special summer projects, 1966; 3 folders (Box 245)
    - St. Lucy guidance, 1966; 3 folders (Box 245)
    - St. Lucy individual guidance, 1966; 4 folders (Box 245)
    - Summer study center, 1966; 2 folders (Box 245)
    - Study Center
      - #1 and #2, 1965-1966; 4 folders
      - Code, 1966 (Box 245)
      - Control group, 1964-1965 (Box 245)
      - East Side #1, 1965 (Box 245)
      - Intake and control groups codebooks, 1964-1965 (Box 245)
      - Research code, 1966; 2 folders (Box 245)
      - Research code and special summer projects code book, 1966 (Box 245)
      - Termination and evaluation, undated (Box 245)
    - Subsequent contact lists, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 246)
    - Subsequent contacts, 1966-1967; 4 folders (Box 246)
    - Summer language arts, undated; 3 folders (Box 246)
    - Summer preschool, undated; 2 folders (Box 246)
    - Syracuse neighborhood survey, codebook, Betty Baer, 1964 (Box 246)
    - Tallman
      - Base, 1965-1966; 8 folders (Box 246)
      - Base community service, 1965-1967; 6 folders (Box 246)
      - Base community service, 1965-1967; 9 folders (Box 247)
      - Base help center, 1966 (Box 247)
      - Base neighborhood center, Jan 1966 (Box 247)
      - Center individual contact, 1967; 2 folders (Box 247)
      - Day camp intake boys, 1965; 5 folders (Box 247)
      - Day camp intake girls, 1965 (Box 247)
      - Pioneer base, Jan 1966 (Box 247)
      - Study center, 1966; 2 folders (Box 247)
      - Study center and preschool, 1967; 6 folders (Box 247)
      - Summer program, 1966; 2 folders (Box 247)
    - Task report - coding, undated (Box 247)
    - Various card sheets, 1966 (Box 247)
    - Washington-Irving preschool, 1965; 2 folders (Box 247)
    - Washington-Irving preschool Ziegler test, pre and post, Sep 1966 (Box 247)
    - West Side
      - Community services, 1965-1967; 9 folders (Box 247)
      - Community services, 1965-1967; 6 folders (Box 248)
      - Help center, 1966; 7 folders (Box 248)
      - High school equivalency, Apr 1967 (Box 248)
      - Individual contact, Sep 1967 (Box 248)
      - Neighborhood center, Nov 1965 (Box 248)
      - Participant groups, Sep 1967; 2 folders (Box 248)
      - Preschool, 1966; 7 folders (Box 248)
      - Study center, 1965-1967; 11 folders (Box 248)
      - Study center and high school equivalency, 1967; 2 folders (Box 248)
      - Study center preschool, 1966; 3 folders (Box 248)
      - Study center preschool and adult education, 1967 (Box 248)
      - Study center preschool and high school equivalency, 1966 (Box 248)
      - Study center summer program, 1966; 3 folders (Box 248)
    - Wilson Park intake forms, 1965 (Box 248)
    - Wilson Park recreation program, intake forms, 1965 (Box 248)
    - Youths opinion of the Crusade, code sheets, 1966; 2 folders (Box 249)
    - Ziegler code, 1966 (Box 249)
    - Ziegler coding schedule for Caldwell test, undated (Box 249)
    - Ziegler test, Dunbar preschool and post, 1966 (Box 249)
    - Ziegler test, pretest and post test, Aug 1966 (Box 249)
    - Ziegler test, pre and post, Delaware Baptist preschool, 1966 (Box 249)
  - Division files
    - Additional corrective reading forms to be used for training research aids, 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 249)
    - Analysis and evaluation of detached worker programs, undated (Box 249)
    - Applications for employment, research department, 1965 (Box 249)
    - Attention senior staff, Jack Anderson, 1966 (Box 249)
    - Basic information survey, blank, undated (Box 249)
    - Bibliography, 1966 (Box 249)
    - Bookbinders statement, Jack Anderson, 1966 (Box 249)
    - Budget proposed by Research Department, 1966-1967 (Box 249)
    - Can research in social science be both socially useful and scientifically meaningful? Selltiz-Cook, 1966 (Box 249)
    - Census tract, 1967 (Box 249)
    - Census tracts work sheet, key to abbreviations, symbols, and codes, 1967 (Box 249)
    - Characteristics of youth in contact with the employment program, Jack Anderson and John Pelosi, 1966 (Box 249)
    - Conceptualization of social agents between low income and middle class children, 1967 (Box 249)
    - Containment, Co-optation, or Co-determination, Harrington-Desent Autum, 1965 (Box 249)
    - Contents of IBM room files, 1967 (Box 249)
    - Community Action: Instrument of Change, Henry Cohen, 1966 (Box 249)
    - Community Action Program 5 report, research department, 1967 (Box 249)
    - Community Action Program, status reports, 1966 (Box 250)
    - Community leaders in health and welfare services, 1964 (Box 250)
    - Community services contact form, 1966 (Box 250)
    - Community services lists, duplicates and no addresses, 1965 (Box 362)
    - Community services OEO monthly feedback, 1966 (Box 250)
    - Community services participant group, white card, 1967 (Box 250)
    - Community service planning group, green card, 1966 (Box 250)
    - County census tract maps, 1964 (Box 358)
    - Crusade analysis, undated (Box 250)
    - Daily time sheet, 1967 (Box 250)
    - Data collection in program areas, 1965 (Box 250)
    - Data collection instruction, weekly reports, undated (Box 250)
    - Data, employment section, as of 3/1/1965 (Box 250)
    - "Dear friend…" letter, Jack Anderson, 1966 (Box 250)
    - Dear neighborhood youth worker, Jack Anderson, 1966 (Box 250)
    - Delinquency figures for Action Area, 1965 (Box 250)
    - Description of proposed North Side area, 1967 (Box 250)
    - Dropouts by census tracts, 1959-1960 (Box 250)
    - Education, research design, undated (Box 250)
    - Employment figures - 6 months, 1964 (Box 250)
    - Employment list of names, 1967 (Box 250)
    - Employment program - data, 1965 (Box 250)
    - Employment research forms, blank, 1965 (Box 250)
    - Feedback sheets, 1967 (Box 250)
    - Food markets by census tract, 1966 (Box 250)
    - Forms, 1965 (Box 250)
    - Forms used by research in evaluation, 1965 (Box 250)
    - General staff research forms, blank, 1965 (Box 250)
    - Glazier - general typing, 1967 (Box 250)
    - Graphs of high and low income census tracts by sex and age, from 1960 census (Box 358)
    - Green planning group cards, 1967 (Box 250)
    - Guidance program, opinion poll, blank, 1966 (Box 250)
    - Guidelines for research, 1965 (Box 251)
    - Hand guide for Community Development Aides and Secretarial, 1967 (Box 251)
    - Head Start data, 1966 (Box 251)
    - ID letters, 1965 (Box 251)
    - Instructional team members, experience sheet, 1966 (Box 251)
    - Let the Buyer Beware - Do We Pay More?, prepared by the In-service Training by Research Department, 1967 (Box 251)
    - Letter regarding applicants for jobs from Research Aides training, Momoyo Ise, no date, 1967 (Box 251)
    - Letter regarding county survey #1, 1966 (Box 251)
    - Management Information report (Box 251)
    - Management Information System
      - Administration, undated (Box 251)
      - CAP training progress report, 1967 (Box 251)
      - Community services, 1967 (Box 251)
      - Correspondence in, 1967 (Box 251)
      - Head Start, undated (Box 251)
      - Health, undated (Box 251)
      - Housing, undated (Box 251)
      - Manpower progress report, undated (Box 251)
      - Non CAP categories, 1967 (Box 251)
      - Reports and correspondence, 1967 (Box 251)
    - Maps
      - Action areas, 1964; 2 folders (Box 251)
      - Poverty index - city and county, 1960-1962 (Box 251)
      - Syracuse, 1964 (Box 251)
    - Master copies of maps, undated (Box 251)
    - Memos, research department, 1965-1966 (Box 251)
    - Memo to senior staff from the research department, feedback, 1966 (Box 251)
    - Mental health research unit papers, 1965 (Box 251)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966; 4 folders (Box 252)
    - Miscellaneous memos, 1966-1967 (Box 252)
    - Model cities program, research department, Moko Ise, 1967 (Box 252)
    - Monthly time records, research, undated (Box 252)
    - New study center forms, blanks, 1965-1966 (Box 252)
    - OEO management information reporting system, 1966; 2 folders (Box 252)
    - OEO monthly report, final form from research to CFO, 1966-1967 (Box 252)
    - Onondaga County Research Development, 1967 (Box 252)
    - Outline for the departmental functions, undated (Box 252)
    - "The Participation of Professionals in Community Decisions for Health and Welfare Services," by Charles V. Willie, 1965 (Box 252)
    - Personnel
      - Full time, 1967 (Box 252)
      - Inventory, codebooks, 1967 (Box 252)
      - Inventory forms, 1967 (Box 252)
      - Policy, 1966 (Box 252)
      - Potential, 1967 (Box 252)
      - Resumes, 1967 (Box 252)
      - Terminations, 1967; 5 folders (Box 253)
    - Police files - delinquency profile, 1965 (Box 253)
    - Police files - tables - control registry, 1965 (Box 253)
    - Police files - tabulations, 1965 (Box 362)
    - Police records, pre-March employment roster, 1961-1965 (Oversize 1)
    - The Politics of Poverty, Michael Harrington, 1965 (Box 204)
    - Population trends, 1960-1967 (Box 204)
    - Preschool data, 1966 (Box 204)
    - Preschool inventory - lists of children, 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 204)
    - Program development, undated (Box 254)
    - Proposed northside area, 1966-1967 (Box 254)
    - Public housing (Box 254)
    - Public school requests for research, 1957 (Box 254)
    - Publication rights, use of data, 1965 (Box 254)
    - Reading evaluation, undated; 2 folders (Box 254)
    - Reading research forms, blank, 1965 (Box 254)
    - Rehabilitation research forms, blank, 1965 (Box 254)
    - Reply forms, undated (Box 254)
    - Reproductions, program division, 1967 (Box 254)
    - Request for supplies, 1965-1966 (Box 254)
    - Research Aide personnel files, 1967; 2 folders (Box 254)
    - Research applicants, 1967 (Box 254)
    - Research department, correspondence, 1966 (Box 254)
    - Research department, staff meeting, Mar 1966 (Box 254)
    - Research design (overall), 1964 (Box 254)
    - Research division, inter office letters, 1967 (Box 254)
    - Research feedback, 1965-1967; 3 folders (Box 255)
    - Research feedback, community services, blank, undated; 3 folders (Box 255)
    - Research file contents, 1967 (Box 255)
    - Research function at CFO, 1966 (Box 255)
    - The research function at CFO, Jack Anderson, appendix, Field of Action research, undated (Box 255)
    - Research planning, 1965 (Box 255)
    - Research proposal for the evaluation of community action program projects, 1964 (Box 255)
    - Research staff monthly reports, 1965-1967 (Box 255)
    - Research training program, 1967 (Box 255)
    - School - annual census and enrollment report, 1964 (Box 255)
    - School record, Moko Ise, 1965 (Box 255)
    - Socio economic indicators of poverty levels, undated (Box 255)
    - Socio economic ranks, education, 1966 (Box 255)
    - Staff discussion, 1965-1967 (Box 255)
    - Staff meeting, Mar 1966 (Box 255)
    - Statistical data, 1967 (Box 256)
    - Student referral data, 1966 (Box 256)
    - Study Center
      - Evaluation, 1966; 2 folders (Box 256)
      - Feedback, 1966 (Box 256)
      - Information lists, 1965 (Box 256)
      - Intake card, 1966 (Box 256)
      - Preliminary data, 1966 (Box 256)
      - Research forms, blank (Box 256)
    - Summary listing of research department project reports for 1966-1967 (Box 256)
    - Summer language arts program, research forms, blank, 1965 (Box 256)
    - Summer preschool program research forms, blank, 1965 (Box 256)
    - Summer programs, 1965 (Box 256)
    - Summer recreation program, 1967 (Box 256)
    - Summer re-entry program research forms, 1965 (Box 256)
    - Surveyors applications, 1965 (Box 256)
    - Syracuse University research corporation, 1967 (Box 256)
    - Table of contents for research projects, summaries, reports, 1967 (Box 256)
    - Tallman lists, duplicates and no addresses, 1965 (Box 362)
    - Team guidance research forms, blank, 1965 (Box 256)
    - Total population of the five action areas, 1967 (Box 256)
    - Trainees regarding research and employment program, 1966 (Box 256)
    - Urban improvement in Syracuse (Box 256)
    - Urban renewal, relocation, 1965 (Box 256)
    - US Census of Housing: 1960 City Blocks, Syracuse, NY, 1961 (Box 256)
    - Views: Housing Isn't a Cure-All; Simple Rules for Tenants, McGarry, Herald Journal, 1964 (Box 256)
    - Vital statistics, Syracuse, 1965 (Box 256)
    - Vital statistics, Department of Health, Syracuse, 1963-1964 (Box 256)
    - The War on Poverty, Political Pornography, Saul Alinksky, 1965 (Box 256)
    - Welfare data, 1963-1964 (Box 256)
  - Interviews
    - Carrie Nellons, interviews, expenses, 1966 (Box 256)
    - Instructions for interviewers, 1966 (Box 256)
    - Interview schedule
      - Guidance Counselor, 1966 (Box 256)
      - Instructional Specialist, 1966 (Box 256)
      - Instructional Specialist, more than one school, 1966 (Box 256)
      - Teacher Aide, 1966 (Box 257)
      - Team Planning, Ise Moko, teachers, 1966 (Box 257)
    - Interviewer #4, Lucy Armstrong, 1966 (Box 257)
    - Interviews, petty cash, 1966 (Box 257)
    - Interviews with County Officials regarding poverty program, 1964 (Box 257)
    - Jeanette Griffin, interviews, expenses, 1966 (Box 257)
    - Marion Wavle, interviews, expenses, 1966 (Box 257)
    - Pat Masters, interviews, expenses, 1966 (Box 257)
    - Study Center questions, 1966 (Box 257)
    - Teachers interviews, 1966 (Box 257)
    - Teachers interview, Moko Ise, undated (Box 257)
    - Teacher interview, numbering system, 1966 (Box 257)
  - Program Development
    - Administrative and Program Information, 1964-1965 (Box 257)
    - Agriculture, 1966 (Box 257)
    - Anti-poverty programs, undated (Box 257)
    - CAP 7-III evaluation, revised program development, 1965 (Box 257)
    - Correspondence (Box 257)
      - Ann Gregory (Program Development), 1967 (Box 257)
      - David Givner, 1967 (Box 257)
      - David Lindberg, 1967 (Box 257)
      - Employment division (Pierce building), 1967 (Box 257)
      - Howard Belt, 1967 (Box 257)
      - Ralph Johnson, 1966-1967 (Box 257)
      - Syracuse Urban Renewal Agency, 1967 (Box 257)
      - William Smith (Field Operations), 1967 (Box 257)
    - Educational materials, 1966; 3 folders (Box 258)
    - Final report to the Division of Special Programs, Office of Manpower, Automation, and Training, US Dept of Labor, 1964 (Box 258)
    - Follow up, 1967 (Box 258)
    - High school dropouts, 1965 (Box 258)
    - History of towns, undated (Box 258)
    - John Acousta, organizations and institutions in county - their potency in general and in particular areas, 1965 (Box 258)
    - John Acousta, program development memos and letters, 1965-1966 (Box 258)
    - Location of the poor in the county, 1965 (Box 258)
    - Memos, 1964-1965 (Box 258)
    - Memos and letters, 1965-1966 (Box 258)
    - Onondaga Indian Reservation, 1965-1966 (Box 259)
    - Onondaga Indian Reservation report, 1966 (Box 259)
    - Planning structure and process, undated (Box 259)
    - Potent people in the county, their attitude toward the poverty program, undated (Box 259)
    - Potent people in the county, their information on social problems in the area, undated (Box 259)
    - Potent people in the county, their perception of the poor in their community, undated (Box 259)
    - Potent people in the county, their probable receptivity to making resources available, undated (Box 259)
    - Program Development Specialist and Assistant, recruitment letter, 1967 (Box 259)
    - Program information, 1966; 2 folders (Box 259)
    - Program interview with Camillus Supervisor William Bush, undated (Box 259)
    - Program suggestions, 1966 (Box 259)
    - Proposed programs, 1966 (Box 259)
    - Proposals and programs, 1966; 2 folders (Box 259)
    - Reports and memos, 1966-1967 (Box 259)
    - Reported of Phase One General Survey of Onondaga County Area, circa 1966 (Box 259)
    - Reported of Phase One General Survey of Onondaga County Area, completed with final revision, circa 1966 (Box 260)
    - Rural programs, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 260)
    - Social Service exchange information, 1965 (Box 260)
    - Summer recreation program, 1967 (Box 362)
    - Syracuse Department of Health, 1966 (Box 260)
    - Town of
      - Cicero, interviews, 1965 (Box 260)
      - Clay, interviews, 1965 (Box 260)
      - Dewitt, interviews, 1966 (Box 260)
      - Elbridge, interviews, 1965 (Box 260)
      - Geddes, interviews, 1965 (Box 260)
      - Jordan, interviews, 1965 (Box 260)
      - LaFayette, interviews, 1965 (Box 260)
      - Manlius, interviews, 1965 (Box 260)
      - Marcellus, interviews, 1965 (Box 260)
      - Onondaga, interviews, 1966 (Box 260)
      - Pompey, interviews, 1966 (Box 260)
      - Skaneateles, interviews, 1965 (Box 260)
      - Tully, interviews, 1965 (Box 260)
    - Town reports
      - Bibliography and glossary of terms, 1966 (Box 260)
      - General town reports of Onondaga County, introduction, 1966 (Box 260)
      - Town of Camillus, 1966 (Box 260)
      - Town of Cicero, 1966 (Box 260)
      - Town of Clay, 1966 (Box 260)
      - Town of Dewitt, 1966 (Box 260)
      - Town of Elbridge, 1966 (Box 260)
      - Towns of Fabius, Otisco, Spafford, and Tully, 1965 (Box 260)
      - Town of Geddes, 1966 (Box 260)
      - Town of LaFayette and Pompey, 1966 (Box 260)
      - Town of Lysander and Van Buren, circa 1966 (Box 260)
      - Town of Manlius, 1966 (Box 260)
      - Town of Marcellus, 1966 (Box 260)
      - Town of Onondaga, 1966 (Box 261)
      - Town of Salina, 1966 (Box 261)
      - Town of Skaneateles, 1966 (Box 261)
      - Village of Baldwinsville, 1966 (Box 261)
    - Welfare Law Bulletin, 1966
  - Reports
    - Basic data pertaining to neighborhood board areas, George Hall, 1966 (Box 261)
    - Causes of blight (in Syracuse), 1967 (Box 261)
    - Characteristics of youth in contact with the employment program, 1966 (Box 261)
    - Characteristics of youth in contact with the employment program (report #2), 1966; 2 folders (Box 261)
    - Comments on report of the community problems study committee, Moko Ise, 1967 (Box 261)
    - Community Action: Past, Present, Future, Kravits, 1966 (Box 261)
    - The conception of time and events, 1967 (Box 261)
    - Consumer report, 1967 (Box 261)
    - Demographic study, poverty areas, 1966 (Box 261)
    - Description of proposed North Side area, 1967 (Box 261)
    - Education reports, 1967 (Box 261)
    - Employment forms and reports, 1965 (Box 261)
    - Employment report and data, 1965 (Box 261)
    - Employment report from county and neighborhood survey, 1967 (Box 261)
    - Ethnicity of individuals using neighborhood centers of the Crusade for Opportunity, 1967 (Box 261)
    - Evaluation of CFO employment programs, 1966 (Box 261)
    - Flanagan report to OMAT, 1965 (Box 262)
    - Indexes and Perceptions of Poverty in Suburban and Rural Areas of Onondaga County, 1966 (Box 262)
    - Information on target areas, 1962-1966 (Box 262)
    - Interventions by community services personnel with police, schools, welfare, and other agencies through June 30, 1965 (Box 262)
    - Let the Buyer Beware - Do We Pay More?, 1967 (Box 262)
    - Madison area project: purpose, process, and product as it relates to Madison Junior High School, report, 1964 (Box 262)
    - Madison Jr. High report, 1963-1964 (Box 262)
    - Management information report, Dec 1966 (Box 262)
    - MIS reports, 1967; 5 folders (Box 262)
    - Monthly reports, 1967 (Box 262)
    - Parents perception of the Syracuse School Bussing Program, Momoyo Ise, 1966; 3 folders (Box 262)
    - Proposed Adult Education and Community Orientation Program," People's AME Zion Church, undated
    - Quarterly report, 1967 (Box 263)
    - Report on the Community Development Task Force, Jack Anderson, 1964 (Box 263)
    - Report of the community problems study committee, Moko Ise, 1967 (Box 263)
    - Report on Management Information System, 1966 (Box 263)
    - Report on the preschool program, Moko Ise, Dec 1966 (Box 263)
    - Report #1 on Preschool: Comparative Study of Conceptualization of Social Agents between Low Income Children and Middle Class Children, 1966 (Box 263)
    - Report on terminations, undated (Box 263)